One more thing.
I fix this later on in the project, although as I'm recording this in the future, when you click play
right now, as soon as I start the game, the lighting kind of changes and looks kind of weird in order
to fix that, if you just go to edit and go project settings.
And then if you look for auto exposure and just leave this unchecked and that will make it so the lighting
kind of doesn't change.
And then the game may be looking kind of like dark.
If you want to change the brightness of the game, what you can do is go over to the player BP, and
just select the camera.
And here under details, if you look for brightness to check this min ev and this max ev and basically
the lower you make this value, the brighter the game is going to be.
And the higher you make this value, the darker the game is going to be.
So if I make this look like -0.5 and -0.5 and just go compile and save the game is going to be kind
of bright ish.
So it's kind of looks kind of bright ish.
If I change this to be something like two and two, then the game is going to be kind of dark.
Darker compared to how it was before.
So that looks pretty dark.
So you can just kind of change that if you want to affect the lighting.
Towards the end of the game, I go over the lighting settings I use, although I just wanted to mention
this to you now, as some of you were asking it to me earlier, I'm just going to change this to be
0.6 for now though.
And one more thing with the lighting.
Plus, this map looks kind of dark in Unreal Engine.
You can use the control and elbon If you set both of those keys at the same time, you can use that
to kind of control where the sun is.
And that can kind of affect the brightness of the level.
So you can just play around with that if you want to like change how bright the level is.
So right now it's kind of a bit brighter because I've moved the sun, But you can use control L to kind
of move the positioning of the sun in your game.